<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mantras on Bhakta Handbook</title>
    <link>https://krsnaloka.github.io/en/mantras/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mantras on Bhakta Handbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Das gehört alles Krsna</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krsnaloka.github.io/en/mantras/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gayatri-Mantra</title>
      <link>https://krsnaloka.github.io/en/mantras/gayatri-mantra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krsnaloka.github.io/en/mantras/gayatri-mantra/</guid>
      <description>[Weitergeleitet von Hare Krishna Maha Mantra]
DO YOU KNOW HOW MANY DEITIES ARE MENTIONED IN GAYATRI MANTRA?
There are 26 gods in gayatri mantra
That is why it’s called the mother of all mantras
 OM
Tat- Ganesh
Sa- Narasimha
Vi- Vishnu
Tu-siva
Va- krishna
Re-radha
Ni- lakshmi
Yam- agni
Bha- indra
Rgo- saraswati
De- durga
Va- hanuman
Sya- prithvi
Dhee- surya
Ma- Sriram
Hi-seetha
Dhi- chandra
Yo- yama
Ya-brahma</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Narasimha Gayatri</title>
      <link>https://krsnaloka.github.io/en/mantras/narasimha_gayatri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krsnaloka.github.io/en/mantras/narasimha_gayatri/</guid>
      <description>[Weitergeleitet von SHIVA KUMAR]
 🙏उग्रं वीरं महाविष्णुं ज्वलन्तं सर्वतोमुखम्।
नृसिंहं भीषणं भद्रं मृत्युमृत्युं नमाम्यहम् ॥
 Ugram Viram Maha Vishnum Jvalantam Sarvato Mukham Nirisimham Bhishanam Bhadram Mrutyur Mrutyum Namamy Aham
Meaning: May Lord Narasimha who is highly ferocious and brave and the emanation of Lord Maha Vishnu, full of effulgence, terrific and auspicious and the death of death bless us as we bow down to Him.
Shri Vishnu&amp;rsquo;s preserving, restoring, and protecting powers have been manifested in the world in a series of ten earthly incarnations known as avatars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shri Nrisimha Mahamantra</title>
      <link>https://krsnaloka.github.io/en/mantras/nrisimha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krsnaloka.github.io/en/mantras/nrisimha/</guid>
      <description>go to indiatimes.com
  He who recites that spell (ugram viram mahavisnum), recites all the Vedas, he offers all sacrifices, he bathes in all sacred bathing places, he is released from the great sins and from the secondary sins, he attains great preeminence in sacred knowledge (great holiness), he purifies his relatives (the people of his line), his first ancestors from Brahman forth and his descendants unto the end of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Different names of Sri Hari</title>
      <link>https://krsnaloka.github.io/en/mantras/krsna_names/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krsnaloka.github.io/en/mantras/krsna_names/</guid>
      <description>Sri Krishna with the meaning   Yogeshwara: Somebody who can understand the mind of anything and anybody. Sri Hari is the Parama (ultimate) Prabhu (leader / father). That&amp;rsquo;s why Sri Krishna is known as Yogeshwara. Also Yogeshwara means somebody who has the ultimate richness and power (which cannot be compared even with any other Demi Gods - even like Sri Brahma Deva, Rudhra Deva and even Sri Mahalakshmi Devi). Yogeshwara: Yogi = Ultimate mind reader / Yoga performer, Ishwara - Supreme to everybody and everything.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
